Abraham Yang

Frontend Web Developer



I am a software engineer and frontend web developer speciallizing in the Javascript and css, familiarizing with React framework and Material UI library. I build successful websites and web apps that are fast, easy to use, and coded with the same eye for detail as a designer, and have abundance of experience on minisite for automobiles, meetings and devices.

PERSONAL

+86 159-2109-8538



abram.yang@outlook.com



Minhang, Shanghai, China



Mandarin Chinese, English

SKILLS

Javascript(ES6)



React.js

MaterialUI

Photoshop



EDM) Webpack)



jQuery

Gulp

GatsbyJS

NodeJS

Handlebar.js

Vue.js

EDUCATION

Shanghai Dianji University

Electronic Engineering

Bachelor's degree 2019

Certificates:

College English Test Brand 4 (CET4) College English Test Brand 6 (CET6)

College Computer Rank Level 2

Web Design of CITT Level 3

Scholarships: Level 2 -x2 / Level 3 -x5

HOBBIES









Traveling

Photography Gaming

Calligraphy

EMPLOYMENT

Software Enginner @ Publicissapient, Shanghai

Huawei Honor Minisite: Microsoft365 challenge

The minisite made by React framework and Material UI library post the race about the microsoft 365 user to create excellent subjects and let them upload their works to backend to earn a reward.

IQOS EDM:

Build eDM template to implement on salesforce CRM by Mjml eDM framework.

DS Automobile:

Collaborate with my team to build a fast, fade animated, artistic and responsive website.

Huawei MWC2020 Minisite

Follow the design of UI/UX designers to build a faster, animated and functional website. This website is used for display the video and news of the Live, and be able to filter the video by tags.

Huawei History Minisite:

This website is only for landscape view, whatever users rotate the phone would show the same view, and shown as a storyline to users for telling the history of Huawei.

Huawei MBBF Minisite template:

This website is used for display the video and news of the MBBF, and show the location of the exhibition

Huawei GT Minisite:

This website display a list of Huawei store, and link to tencent map for navigation.

SAICMotor Roewe&MG:

Maintain the official website and build vehicle pages periodically.

Software Enginner Intern @ Publicissapient, Shanghai 2019.04 - 2019.07

Marriott CN official website

I participated in the Marriott CN Locale Project with Indian team. Baidu Map development implement on Marriott, read the the documentation and write English document for introduction for wechat JSSDK.







wechat: abramyangcn







Project Details

Huawei Honor Minisite: Microsoft365 challenge

Tech stack: React.js, Sass, Material UI, Axios.js, Swiper.js Tools: Photoshop, Zeplin

I completed the webpage in 5 days independently. Once I got the design, I imported it to PS and exported the cuts to Zeplin for design version control. For the coding, I use hook in react, components in Material UI which can save my lifetime to fast build pages, but the interfaces from backend were hard to debug because of their imperfect documentation. I worked over time to ensure the project complete on time.

IQOS EDM

Tech stack: Mjml, Gulp

Tools: Photoshop Zeplin, Litmus

During this project, I worked with Indian tech team and Japanese design team. My role was to provide the html email template which I start with mjml framework to fast build for different days for the whole journey, and build for responsive design by media query, use Litums to debug email for each platform. I attended the daily stand up meeting to report my work, disscused to backend for better implementation on EDM.

DS Automobile

Tech stack: ¡Query, Webpack, Gulp, Sass, Swiper.js, list.js, wow.js Tools: Sketch, Zeplin, Google Analytics

During this project, I build the webpage that contains vertical fade in animate, carousel herobanner with video and filter and search dealer list. It is worth mentioning that video can trim by adding '#t<begin>,<end>' to the end of the video source link and it will load the trim part only as well. Moreover, the dealers in dealer page can display in baidu map, and be able to click to show the info window, filter by province, city and category of dealers and fuzzy search.

Huawei MWC2020&MBBF Minisite

Tech stack: ¡Query, Swiper.js

Tools: Sketch, Zeplin, Google Analytics

This project was highly focused on the UI and UX, so I wrote lots of style, and javascipt for animation. I refactory the Swiper feature, made card collapse effect, card flip effect and video preview feature. It just an animating and responsive static webpage template, so what client can be easier to deploy was that I extract the data to a Javascript Object orderly. That way can be easier to edit and maintain for clients.

Huawei History & Huawei GT Minisite

Tech stack: Vue.js, Sass, wechat JSSDK

Tools: Photoshop, Premiere, Zeplin, Excel, Google Analytics Both webpages were an single page with Vue.js.

For Huawei History, there was a video as a background in homepage, to realize that, I clipped a short video from the 'Who is Huawei' documentary for desktop view, and exported every frame to images so that be able to apply on canvas for mobile view, Gifs requiered as well. The wechat SDK was used to customize sharing. For Huawei GT, I used a district picker, exported excel convert to json for rendering the list of Huawei store, and implement tencent map on the page. The wechat SDK was to wake up third party map.

SAICMotor Roewe&MG:

Tech stack: ¡Query, Sass

Tools: Photoshop, Google Analytics, VM horizon

It was a long term project, I had to maintain the official website, do SEO optimization, build webpage for the models. Because the client didn't develop the CMS, so some edit works was send to me. There were lots of vendor in SAIC, as we were one of them, the one more thing was that I have to contact with the other vendor to revert code because there was no version control tools, no PM for me and they always covered our code.

During the time, I interviewed a college student for internship who can help me to maintain the official website.

Marriott CN officail website

Tech stack: Vue.js, Sass, wechat JSSDK

Tools: Photoshop, Google Analytics, VM horizon

During this experience, I participated in the Marriott CN Locale Project with Indian team.

Basically, the component which contains baidumap and the Wechat share of proof of concept was assigned to me, and I attended the voice meetingand sent 2 e-mails every day to report my progress for better coordinate.

Baidu Map development on Marriott: read the documentation of Backbone is and handlebars is to develop, Features below:

Focus on hotel card to pin the hotel marker

Customize the info window cloned from hotel card

Customize the cluster and its info window

Show the duplicate hotel marker

Click the marker to show popup.

Wechat JS-SDK: Read the the documentation and write English document for introduction.













杨杨 Abraham Yang

前端开发工程师



本人是一名软件工程师和前端web开发人员,擅长Javascript和css,熟悉React框架和Material UI库。主要建立网 站和网页应用程序,这些网站和应用程序速度快,易于使用,编码时对细节有着与设计师相同的眼光。在汽车行业、 会议和移动设备的网站上有丰富的经验。

个人信息

+86 159-2109-8538

abram.yang@outlook.com

中国 上海市 闵行区

普通话,英语

技能

Javascript(ES6)

Sass

React.js

MaterialUI

Photoshop

MJML

EDM)

GatsbyJS

jQuery

Webpack

Gulp

NodeJS

Handlebar.js

Vue.js

毕业院校

上海电机学院

电子信息工程

本科 2019

证书:

全国大学英语4级(CET4)

全国大学英语6级(CET6)

上海市计算机2级

网页设计3级职业技能证书

奖学金: 二等奖 --x2 / 三等奖 --x5

兴趣爱好







工作经验

前端开发软件工程师@阳狮集团Publicissapient,上海 2019.07 - 至今

华为荣耀 Minisite: Microsoft365 challenge

此页面使用了React框架以及Material UI库,全球用户可以上传自己的作品来参加创作比 赛,荣耀的后台审核完毕之后公布获奖者。

IQOS EDM 邮件营销:

与日本、新加坡以及印度团队协作,使用了MJML框架来写edm的模版,在salesforce marketing cloud 上部署。

法国 DS 汽车:

在团队协作下完成了DS汽车官网的开发,页面非常迅速,法式艺术以及响应式。

华为世界移动通信大会 MWC2020 Minisite:

遵循UI/UX设计师的设计,构建一个更快、更生动、更具功能性的网站。这个网站用于展示示 现场的视频和新闻,并能够通过标签过滤视频。

华为历史 Minisite:

本网站仅为横向浏览,无论用户旋转手机,都会显示相同的视图,并以故事情节向用户展示 华为的历史。

华为Gentle Monster 眼镜:

本网站显示了华为门店的列表,并且引导用户至腾讯地图导航至门店地址。

华为全球移动宽带论坛 MBBF Minisite template:

该网站用于展示MBBF的视频和新闻,并显示展位的位置。

上汽集团荣威&名爵:

维护官方网站,定期上新车辆页面。

软件工程师实习@阳狮集团Publicissapient,上海 2019.04 - 2019.07

万豪集团中国官方网站

在此经历中,我参与了万豪中国的官网开发,很快速的融入了印度团队。我被派发了百度地 图和微信分享这两个任务,修改含有谷歌地图的组件为百度地图,并且进行二次开发。







wechat: abramyangcn







项目内容

华为荣耀 Minisite: Microsoft365 challenge

技术栈:React.js, Sass, Material UI, Axios.js, Swiper.js 工具:Photoshop, Zeplin

我在5天内独立完成了网页。获得设计后,将其导入到PS中,并将剪 切内容导出到Zeplin以进行设计版本控制。编码时,我在Material UI 中使用hook in react组件,可以节省我的时间以快速构建页面,但是 由于客户后端的文档不完善,所以接口很难调试。我加班工作以确保 项目准时上线。

法国 DS 汽车:

技术栈: ¡Query, Webpack, Gulp, Sass, Swiper.js, list.js, wow.js 工具: Sketch, Zeplin, Google Analytics

在这个项目期间,我建立了一个网页,其中包含动画,轮播banner, 垂直淡入每个元素,以及视频,过滤器和搜索经销商列表。值得一提 的是,可以通过在视频源链接的末尾添加'#t <begin>, <end>'来修 剪视频,并且也只会加载修剪部分。此外,经销商页面中的经销商可 以显示百度地图,并且可以显示信息窗口,按省,城市和经销商类别 过滤以及模糊搜索。

Huawei History & Huawei GT Minisite

技术栈: Vue.js, Sass, wechat JSSDK 工具: Photoshop, Premiere, Zeplin, Excel, Google Analytics

两个网页都是使用Vue.is的单页面。

对于华为历史项目,主页中有一段视频作为背景,为了实现这个功 能,我从"Who is Huawei"纪录片中剪辑了一段短片,用于桌面视图, 然后将每帧导出到图像中,以便能够在canvas上画出来作为移动端 视频效果,并且还制作了Gif。微信SDK用于自定义共享卡片。 对于华为Gentle Monster 眼镜项目,我使用了区域选择器,将excel 转换为json导出以渲染华为商店列表,并在页面上渲染了腾讯地图。 微信SDK是用来唤醒第三方地图的。

IQOS EDM 邮件营销:

技术栈: Mjml, Gulp 工具: Photoshop Zeplin, Litmus

在此项目期间,我曾与印度技术团队和日本设计团队合作。我的角色 是制作以mjml为框架的html电子邮件模板,以便在整个客户旅程中 快速构建不同日期的内容,并通过媒体查询为响应设计进行构建,并 使用Litums调试每个平台的电子邮件。我参加了每日会议,汇报了我 的工作,并讨论了如何在EDM上更好地实施后端。

Huawei MWC2020&MBBF Minisite

技术栈: jQuery, Swiper.js 工具: Sketch, Zeplin, Google Analytics

项目为华为世界移动通信大会和华为全球移动宽带论坛 这个项目高度专注于UI和UX,因此我编写了很多样式,并为动画编 写了Javascipt。我二次开发了Swiper功能:制作了卡片折叠效果 和卡片翻转效果,还有视频预览功能。它是一个动画响应的静态网 页模板,因此可以更轻松地部署客户端是我将数据有序地提取到 Javascript对象中。这样可以更轻松地为客户进行编辑和维护。

上汽集团荣威&名爵:

技术栈: jQuery, Sass

工具: Photoshop, Google Analytics, VM horizon

这是一个长期的项目,我的工作都是维护官方网站,进行SEO优化, 为模型建立网页。由于客户未开发CMS,因此一些编辑工作派发给

上汽中有很多供应商,我们是其中的一员,因为没有版本控制工具, 没有PM,而且他们总是覆盖我们的代码。我必须与其他供应商联系 以还原代码。

在这段时间里,我还面试了一位大学生实习,他可以帮助我维护官 方网站。

万豪集团中国官方网站

技术栈: Vue.js, Sass, wechat JSSDK

工具: Photoshop, Google Analytics, VM horizon

在此经历中,我参与了万豪中国的官网开发,很快速的融入了印度团队。我被派发了百度地图和微信分享这两个任务,修改含有谷歌地图的组件为百 度地图,并且进行二次开发。每天为了更好的团队协作,通过电话会议,撰写邮件来报告每天的进度。

百度地图: 为了熟悉项目技术栈,我阅读了backbone.js和 handlebars.js的文档,以下是地图开发的要求:

点击列表中酒店卡片以显示标注 自定义信息窗口内容为酒店卡片 点聚合,点聚合的信息窗口自定义 优化同一地点多个酒店的标注

点击标注来弹出弹框

Wechat JS-SDK: 阅读微信官方文档并复述,撰写一篇总结性markdown英文文档。











